HotOrNotCreated by Qing Chen on 3/6/13. Copyright (c) 2013 Qing Chen. All rights reserved.Description:In this game, the player log in the Facebook account and got a question like "Who's more fun" randomly, then pick up a friend between to friends options. After picking 10 friends the result will show how much points each friend get according to how many times the player pick that friends. Then the player can touch the restart button to restart the game.Some highlights:- The the mainview showing questions and process, and the subview that show friends images is instantiated only once per game round.- If number of friends is larger than an amount (pre-defined as 15), friends will be picked up in that range, so that the situation that none same friend occur through the game is prevented.- The questions are dynamic and randomly selected every time the game is restarted.If there is any question, please contact me.Email: qingchen@usc.eduTel.: 213-453-6655